[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lifting incredibly slowly builds incredibly big muscles. Lifting super slowly produces superlong workouts.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of Wolfgang Pucks food handlers tested positive for Hepatitis A. What was the event Puck was catering that possibly exposed hundreds of people to Hepatitis.", "correct_answer": "Sports Illustrated annual swimsuit issue party", "incorrect_answers": ["Academy Awards", "Playboys Playmate of the Year celebration", "The Tony Awards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played trail boss Gil Favor in the long-running television western series Rawhide?", "correct_answer": "Eric Fleming", "incorrect_answers": ["Adam West", "Sheb Wooley", "Jock Mahoney"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote and performed a song featuring the lyrics: I just want your extra time and your kiss?", "correct_answer": "Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["Madonna", "Michael Jackson", "Kylie Minogue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do the Korean, the Japanese and the Chinese call Jupiter?", "correct_answer": "Wood star", "incorrect_answers": ["Iron fist", "Ice cube", "Fire ball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character stated, The Dark side I sense in you?", "correct_answer": "Yoda", "incorrect_answers": ["Obi-Wan", "Mace Windu", "Anakin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of Moa are known to have existed?", "correct_answer": "11-15", "incorrect_answers": ["3-5", "5-7", "10-13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where are vampire bats mostly found?", "correct_answer": "Mexico, Central America and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Asia", "Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This constellation in the Northern Hemisphere was named after a Greek mythological figure, whose name is translated as ruler over men.", "correct_answer": "Andromeda", "incorrect_answers": ["Centaurus", "Cassiopeia", "Hercules"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of The Eagles lead singer and drummer who wrote the song The Boys of Summer?", "correct_answer": "Don Henley", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Walsh", "Tim Schmit", "Glen Frey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where and when does the story in the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth begin?", "correct_answer": "Edinburgh, Scotland, 1880", "incorrect_answers": ["Stockholm, Sweden, 1890", "London, England, 1900", "Oslo, Norway, 1860"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the recipe for the Tiramisu cake originate?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "United States", "Spain"]}]